<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>undergrad | Joey&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/tags/undergrad/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/tags/undergrad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>undergrad</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/img/icon-512.png</url>
      <title>undergrad</title>
      <link>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/tags/undergrad/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Algorithms for White Balancing</title>
      <link>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/whitebalance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/whitebalance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a part time URA(Undergrad Research Assistant) I did with Professor Peter Van Beek. White balance is a vital step in image processing. Due to computation limitations, current white balancing algorithms for cameras are simple. But if we ignore this restriction and apply ML algorithms, state-of-arts performance can be achieved. We explored different machine learning/deep learning methods to improve white balancing performance for photo processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I implemented some popular data augmentation tricks and domain-adaptation
heuristics in MATLAB on existing algorithm and improved the performance
slightly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/mlprivacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/mlprivacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We conduct a survey on privacy in machine learning. First we show examples of how people could use machine learning to invade privacy and how machine learning could cause some unprecedented privacy issues. Then we give the rigorous definition of privacy in mathematics. In the end of this paper, we demonstrate three specific privacy preserving machine learning algorithms and one noise generation method.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variants of Frank-Wolfe algorithm</title>
      <link>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/frankwolfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://JoeyAndBlueWhale.github.io/project/frankwolfe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a part time URA (Undergrad Research Assistant) supervised by Yaoliang Yu. Frank-Wolfe algorithm is a first-order optimization algorithm for constraint optimization problems. The per iteration cost for Frank-Wolfe algorithm is low because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t need the projection step. Recently this algorithm has gained attention again. This project involves in a study of this algorithm and its variants. We also attempted to relax the constraints of some of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I simplified one algorithm and provided a simpler proof.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
